Subaru-kun!
（レム）スバルくん！
（スバル）あっ
Wh-What happened?
（スバル）
何があったんだ 一体
こいつはどういうことなんだ！
What the hell is that thing!?
Subaru-kun, stay down.
スバルくん 立たないで
風除けの加護が切れています
We've lost our Windbreak protection!
What, you still don't get it?
分からないんですか
There's only one massive creature
that can fly through fog like that!
霧の中 あんな巨体で
空を泳ぐ存在なんて１つしかない！
白鯨です！
It's the White Whale!
Rem, can you see the White Whale?
レム 白鯨は見えてるか？
I cannot! It's too dark!
暗すぎて とても無理です
What happened to the other carriages?
（スバル）
ほかの竜車はどうなった？
They seem to have scattered.
散らばって 逃げているようです
But I do not know where they have fled!
どこに逃げたかまでは
分かりません
Damn it!
クッソー せっかく
確保した足だってのに
After we finally found some transportation...
おわーっ！
（オットー）ああ…
（レム）左へ走り抜けて！
Run past it, to the left!
Left, left, left, left, left, left, left!
（オットー）
左 左 左 左…
Eat this!
（レム）くらえー！
D-Did you get it?
や… やりましたか？
くっ… ダメだ
It didn't work.
Wh-Why is it targeting us?
（オットー）
どうして執ように僕らを？
竜車は ほかにもいるでしょうに
There are other carriages out there!
Complaining won't change anything!
恨み言 言ってても
状況は変わらねえ
くっ… 考えろ 考えろ考えろ
Think...
Think. Think, damn it!
打開策だ　何か…
何かないか 何か！
We need a way out!
There has to be a way.
Something! Anything! Anything at all!
Subaru-kun.
（レム）スバルくん
（スバル）えっ
Please take this.
これを受け取ってください
Did you come up with something?
何か思いついたのか？
I shall get off the carriage and intercept it.
レムが竜車を降りて迎撃します
In the meantime, you escape the fog.
その間に スバルくんは
霧を抜け出してください
Otto-sama,
オットー様
please take care of Subaru-kun.
スバルくんをお願いします
約束の報酬は スバルくんが確かに
He has the payment we promised you.
P-Payment?
ほ… 報酬？ 今はそれどころじゃ
命あっての物種ですよ
That's the least of our worries now!
Getting out alive comes first!
Subaru-kun, I am not very smart,
スバルくん レムは頭が悪いので
こんな案しか思いつきません
so this is the only plan I can think of.
どうか
Please...
H-Hold on, Rem!
待てよ レム
行かせねえ 行かせねえぞ！
I won't let you! I won't let you go!
If...
お前が…
お前まで死んだら 俺は…
If you also die, I'll...
I believe I was born for this very moment.
レムは 今 この時のために
生まれてきたんですね
What are you talk—
何を言って… うっ
Rem...
レ… ム… 何して…
What did you...
It will be all right.
大丈夫です
I shall always be watching over you.
レムはずっと スバルくんの後ろで
見守っていますから
Where's Rem?
レムは？
Natsuki-san, you're awake?
（オットー）
ナツキさん 目が覚めましたか？
Please don't move.
動かないでください
地竜は今も全力走行中で―
The land dragon's still running at full speed!
I don't have time to worry about you!
ナツキさんに配慮してる
余裕はないんですから
Who cares about that!?
そんなことはどうでもいい
レムは レムはどうした！
Where's Rem? What happened to Rem?
答えろ オットー
レムはどうした！
Answer me, Otto! What happened to Rem!?
So we could escape,
僕らの竜車を逃がすために―
she jumped out of the carriage
to intercept the White Whale.
白鯨を迎え撃とうと
竜車を降りました
（スバル）戻れ
Go back.
Huh!?
I said to go back!
戻れっつってんだよ
We have to...
レムを レムを助けるんだ！
今すぐ戻れ！
We have to save Rem!
Go back right now!
Wh-What good will that do?
も… 戻って
どうなるっていうんです
Did you not see how fearsome
that monster, the White Whale, is?
白鯨の あのバケモノの
恐ろしさを見なかったんですか？
It'd just be suicide!
自殺行為ですよ
I saw the monster up close!
あのバケモノを
間近で見ちまったから―
That's why I'm telling you to go back!
戻れっつってんだろうが！
Have you lost your mind!?
頭おかしくなったんじゃないですか
あなたは
You want to squander
the small hope that she left us?
あの子の残してくれた
彼女の気持ちをムダにしますか
Don't you dare talk about Rem!
お前がレムを語るんじゃねえよ！
You abandoned her!
レムを見捨てるようなお前に―
You have no right to talk about her!
あいつのこと
語る資格なんざあるか！ 戻れ！
Turn back!
You still don't understand how
terrifying the White Whale is!?
白鯨がどれだけ恐ろしいか
まだ分からないんですか！
When a punitive force, assembled by
Lugunica, set out to subjugate it,
ルグニカ王国が編成した討伐隊
大征伐の時ですら―
that monster killed the former Sword Saint!
先代剣聖が殺されたような
バケモノですよ
There's no way we can win!
勝てるはずがない！
It killed... the Sword Saint?
剣聖を… 殺した？
I'm weak and so are you.
僕は弱く あなたも弱い
So there's no way we can save that girl.
だから 僕らは
あの女の子を助けられない
But...
（スバル）
だけど レムだって
本当は強くなんかない
I know Rem isn't all that strong either.
For now, we were fortunate to escape it.
今は 幸いにも
逃げ切ったはずですが―
But as long as we're in this mist,
there's no telling when it'll show up again.
霧を抜けるまでは いつどこで
出くわすか分かりません
Otto, watch what you say!
オットー 言い方に気をつけろよ！
Huh? What do you mean, Natsuki-san?
え… 何です ナツキさん
Don't talk like this is some game!
ふざけた言い方するなって
言ったんだよ！
We were "fortunate"!?
“幸いにも”だと！
You must be joking.
冗談じゃねえ
Do you know how Rem felt when she—
レムがどんな気持ちで 俺たちを…
Who is Rem?
レムって 誰のことです？
Huh?
There wasn't anyone with that name
散り散りになった
ほかの行商人の中に―
among the merchants who broke off from us.
そんな名前の人は
いなかったはずですし―
誰の話をしてるんですか？
Who are you talking about?
What do you think you're doing!?
い… いきなり何をするんですか！
Cut the crap...
ふざけるな
You talk about how Rem let us escape,
俺たちを逃がすために残った
レムを指して―
and then ask who she is?
誰のことだなんてふざけんな！
てめえ 殺されたいのか！
Do you have a death wish!?
I'm telling you, I don't know
what you're talking about...
何 言ってんだか
分からないっつってんですよ
What's gotten into you all of a sudden?
何だ あんた
急に変なことを言いだして
Did seeing the White Whale make you go mad?
白鯨を見て
おかしくなったんじゃないですか！
Why? Why!? Why is it so persistent!?
どうして どうして どうして
こんな執ように…
I thought we'd left it behind!
引き離したはずじゃ
何だって僕らばかりを
Why is it only after us?
Even in this darkness...
こんな暗い中で どうして…
Why?
Rem...
（スバル）レム…
Is...
（オットー）
何か… 何か目印でも
あるってんですか！
Is there some mark it's following!?
No way.
まさか―
あのバケモノも
That monster is...
The White Whale is...
白鯨も―
a witchfiend too?
魔獣なのか？
Then, it's being drawn to me?
俺の体が引き寄せてるってのか
You can't be serious.
そんな…
Rem,
レム… 俺は そんな…
I... No...
It's my fault!
俺のせいで…
Natsuki-san, please die.
（オットー）
ナツキさん 死んでください
Huh?
It's all your fault!
（オットー）
あな… あなたが悪いんですよ
あなたのせいで追ってくるんだ
I-It's following us because of you!
T-Take responsibility!
せ… 責任 とってくださいよ！
Die! Die, so that I can live!
死んで 死んで僕を助けてー！
I don't wanna die...
死にたくない…
No... I don't wanna die...
イヤだ… 死にたくない…
Help... I don't wanna die!
助け… 死にたくない！
I don't wanna die! I don't wanna die!
死にたくない 死にたくない
死にたくない
I don't wanna die!
No! No!
イヤだ イヤだー！
Help me!
助けてレム イヤだ！
死にたくない！
No! I don't wanna die!
I don't wanna die...
死にたくない…
Huh?
レム…
Rem...
Rem, forgive me.
レム 許してくれ
You're...
お前は…
Where is he?
あいつは… オットーは
Where's Otto?
I see...
そうか
Let's go.
行こう
The forest?
森？
Huh?
（ペトラ）あれ？ スバル？
Subaru?
It is Subaru!
（ミルド）やっぱスバルだ
What happened to you, Subaru?
（ダイン）
どうしたの？ スバル
You're a mess, Subaru. You stink!
（リュカ）
小汚い スバル くさい
You guys...
お前ら…
I wasn't too late this time?
今回は間に合っちまうのかよ…
Subaru?
（ペトラ）スバル！
はっ レム！
Rem—
Why are you so eagerly touching me, Balse?
（ラム）
何を気安く触っているの バルス
I understand that, after a few days away,
you're happy to see me.
数日ぶりに ラムと会えたのが
うれしいのは分かるけど―
But don't instinctively jump on me like that.
そうして本能のままに
飛びかからないで
It's indecent.
いやらしい
Oh...
ああ… そうだよな
Yeah, that's right...
So, Balse, tell me what happened.
それじゃあ バルス
話を聞かせてもらうとするわ
You were in terrible shape.
ひどいありさまだったわ
外れた肩と割れた額―
Your dislocated shoulder, split forehead,
and broken ribs have all been mended.
折れたろっ骨は接いであるけど
無理したら傷が開くわ
But if you move too much, they'll reopen.
I've discarded your muddy, blood-soaked clothes.
血と泥で汚れた服は処分した
Oh, thanks.
ああ そら助かる
Hey, about who healed my wounds...
俺の傷 治してくれたのって…
（ラム）エミリア様よ
It was Emilia-sama.
I don't know what happened
in the capital between you two.
王都で エミリア様と
バルスの間に何があったのか―
I wasn't told, and I'm not interested either.
ラムは聞いてないわ
興味もない
Judging by her reaction,
今の反応を見れば―
I'm sure you did something you shouldn't have.
どうせ バルスが
ろくでもないことをしたんでしょ
That's harsh.
辛辣(しんらつ)だな
I think it's an appropriate assessment.
相応の評価だと思うけど？
Perfect for a loser, afraid to approach
確信に踏み込むのが怖くて―
the heart of the matter,
who'd do anything to put it off a little.
少しでも先延ばしにしようとしてる
ヘタレにはぴったりだわ
Rem is dead.
（スバル）レムが死んだ
I... couldn't do anything.
俺が 何にもできなくて
The fog... the White Whale... appeared on the road.
街道に霧が 白鯨が出たんだ
So, to cover my escape, Rem...
それで レムが俺を
逃がそうとして
But...
でも 俺は霧の中に
取り残されて―
I was left alone in the fog.
And...
それで…
Balse.
（ラム）バルス
レムって―
Rem...
Who is that?
誰のこと？
Huh?
Who is Rem, Balse?
レムって誰のことなの？ バルス
Wh-What do you mean, "who"?
だ… 誰も何も…
バカなこと言うなよ
Don't be ridiculous!
Sh-She's your younger sister!
おま… お前の妹の名前だろ！
You know, Rem! Rem... Rem!
レムだぞ レムだ レムだよ！
ふざけてる場合じゃ…
This is no time for—
ラムに妹なんていないわ
I have no younger sister.
Don't say that!
ふざけんな！
レムがいなけりゃ…
If not for Rem...
That's right!
そうだ
What would you call that whole
mess in the witchfiend forest!?
魔獣の森の騒ぎは
どういう話になんだ
You, Rem, and I fought those witchfiends and—
俺とレムとお前とで魔獣を…
Something is seriously wrong with you, Balse.
本当にどうかしてるわよ バルス
As much as I hate to admit it,
しゃくに障るけれど―
but you were half-responsible
for the ulgarm eradication.
ウルガルムの群れを撲滅できたのは
バルスの手柄が半分―
あとはラムの努力と
ロズワール様のお力が全て
Roswaal-sama and I handled the rest.
This long-lost sister you call
"Rem" has no place in it.
その レムとかいう―
生き別れの妹の
滑り込む隙間なんてないわ
Hey, that's not funny...
冗談にもなってない
Not even the worst nightmares are this crazy!
悪夢にしたって
出来が悪すぎるだろうが！
I am always serious.
（ラム）
ラムはいつだって本気でいるわ
You must be the one who's dreaming.
夢を見ているのは
バルスのほうでしょ
Dreaming...
夢… 夢？
Dreaming?
Dreaming!?
夢だと！
Like hell I am!
ふざけるな！
Balse, you shouldn't stand—
（ラム）
バルス まだ立ち上がったら…
Shut up!
（スバル）
うるせえ！ 黙って…
黙って見てろ！
Just...
Just be quiet and watch!
You've gotta be kidding me...
ウソ… だろ？
Balse, are you satisfied?
（ラム）
バルス 満足した？
Rem isn't...
レムは ここには…
No such person has ever lived in this room.
（ラム）
そんな人は この部屋には
最初からいなかったわ
Go back to your room and sleep.
（ラム）
部屋に戻って 寝ていなさい
Your exhaustion is making you confused.
疲れて いろいろと
混乱してるんでしょ
All I have to do is keep running
and running and running.
（スバル）
逃げて 逃げて
逃げてしまえばいい
What good will running do?
逃げてどうなる…
Lend me your courage, Rem!
勇気を貸してくれ レム！
（エミリア）スバル
Subaru?
Why...
どうして 戻ってきたの？
did you come back?
Let's go.
行こう
We can't stay here!
ここにいちゃいけない
Go? Where?
行くって どこに？
No... Why?
ううん 何のために？
Anywhere that isn't here!
ここじゃない場所なら
どこでもいい！
And if you have to ask why,
I'd say, "For your sake."
何のためかって聞かれたら
お前のためにって俺は答える
I came back for you!
俺はお前のために ここに…
That again, Subaru?
またそれなの スバル
You came back, covered in wounds,
and worried me to death.
急に戻ってきて 傷だらけで
心配までかけて―
Weren't you in the capital so Ferris could treat you?
王都で フェリスの治療を
受けてたはずじゃなかったの？
Why are you here now?
どうして 今 ここにいるの？
If...
If you protest, I'll drag you away
if that's what it takes!
嫌がるなら
無理やりにでも連れて行く
In a few days, you'll see I was right,
whether you want to or not!
何日かすれば―
嫌でも 俺が
正しいんだってことが分かるさ！
So just...
だから！
Wait! Wait, Subaru!
待って 待ってよ スバル
What happened to you?
どうしちゃったの？ スバルは
そんなんじゃなかったじゃない
You weren't this kind of person before.
I thought you...
私はスバルを… なのに…
And yet—
Just shut up and listen to me!
いいから黙って
俺の言うことを聞けよ！
You can't stay here!
ここにいたらダメなんだ！
You'll regret it! I know you will!
お前は後悔する 絶対にする！
No one will be saved.
誰も救われない！
I don't want to suffer and cry anymore!
俺は もう苦しみたくないし
泣きたくなんかないんだよ！
Just do as I say!
俺の言うとおりに
してればいいんだよ！
Then everything will work out! Trust me!
そうすれば
うまくいくんだよ そうなんだ！
Why doesn't anyone understand!?
何で 誰も分かって
くれねえんだよ！
I'm sorry.
ごめんね
I don't understand what you're saying.
スバルが何を言ってるのか
私には分からない
I want to.
分かってあげたいの
だけど―
But right now, I'm not sure I have time for that.
今は そうしてあげられる
時間がないかもしれなくて
There's so much I need to do.
やらなくちゃいけないこと
たくさんあるの
So for now...
だから 今は
It won't work.
（スバル）
うまくいかねえよ
It won't work.
（スバル）
うまくいかない
お前はダメだ 失敗する
You won't make it. You'll fail!
You can't do it. It's no use.
やれるわけがない 全然ダメだ
You're all talk! You can't save anyone, or be saved!
口ばっかりだ
救えない 救われない
You'll keep acting reckless and unreasonable,
ムチャと無謀を積み重ねて―
until the corpses pile up as high
as your thoughtless decisions!
重ねた無理と同じ数だけ
死体の山を見ることになる！
That is your future!
それが お前の未来だ！
Why?
どうして…
Why are you crying like you're in great pain?
どうして―
スバルは そんな苦しそうに
泣いてるの？
After...
俺は… 俺をここまで
送ってくれた… 違う
After she sent me here...
No, after she brought me here, there's...
ここまで連れてきてくれた
レムのために―
There's something I must do for Rem's sake...
レムのためにも
やらなきゃいけないことが…
Rem?
（エミリア）レム…
（スバル）ハッ
You too?
お前も…
You've forgotten Rem too?
（スバル）
お前もレムを忘れるのか…
Subaru?
（エミリア）スバル…
Fine, I'll tell you everything.
（スバル）
いいさ 全部話してやる
If you're all going to forget Rem,
このまま お前らが
レムのことを忘れるなら―
I'd rather expose everything
and end up vomiting blood!
何もかもさらけ出して
血ヘド吐いたほうがマシだ！
If you're coming for me, then come.
（スバル）
来るなら来ればいい
I'll gladly give you my beating heart!
心臓ぐらいくれてやる
エミリア
Emilia...
Yes?
I...
（スバル）
俺は 死に戻りして…
can use Return by Death to—
What was that about?
（スバル）
どういうことだ？ いつもなら…
Usually...
Huh?
Emilia?
エミリア？
Don't... Wha— Huh?
やめ… えっ ちょ え？ あっ
You have the look of someone who believes
they're the most unfortunate soul in the world.
（ベアトリス）
まるで 世界で１番不幸だとでも
言いたげな顔なのよ
Beatrice...
（スバル）ベアトリス
I suppose Bubby won't be coming out.
にーちゃは
出てこれないかしら
Don't worry. I suppose Bubby won't die.
心配しなくても にーちゃは
死んだりしないかしら
He just returned to his original form for now.
１度 本体に戻されてしまった
だけなのよ
I suppose you have something you want to say.
何か言いたいことはあるかしら？
Please kill me. Right here.
ここで殺してくれ
You would ask me to kill you?
ベティーに お前を殺せだなんて
そんなの残酷すぎるかしら
I suppose that's far too cruel.
You understand nothing.
（ベアトリス）
何も分かってない
You understand nothing at all.
お前は何も分かってないのよ
Huh? Beatrice?
え… ベアトリス？
I suppose I won't be granting your wish.
お前の願い事なんか
何ひとつ聞いてやらないかしら
If you want to die, then feel free
to do it on your own.
死にたいなら死にたいで
勝手に死ねばいいのよ
I suppose Betty wants no part of it.
ベティーは願い下げかしら
What are you...
何を…
Everything is already hopeless,
どうせ 何もかもダメだけど
お前に ここにいられたら困るのよ
but your staying here is a problem.
I suppose, at the very least,
I will protect the mansion.
せめて この屋敷だけは
守らせてもらうかしら
Beatrice?
ベアトリス？
Betty is not like Roswaal.
ベティーは
ロズワールとは違うのよ
I don't care if it would secure me a future.
たとえ 未来を得るためでも―
Pain, suffering, fear...
痛いのも 苦しいのも 恐ろしいのも
全てイヤになったかしら
I suppose I've had enough of it all!
I suppose the least you can do
is die out of my sight.
せめて ベティーの見えない所で
死んでしまえばいいかしら
Emilia...
エミ… リア
Sorry... I'm sorry.
ごめんな ごめん
I'm sorry.
ごめん
I'm so sorry...
本当にごめん
Someone...
誰か… 誰でもいい
Anyone...
Please kill me!
殺してくれー！
I've been waiting for you, believer in love.
（ペテルギウス･ロマネコンティ）
お待ちしておりましたデス
寵(ちょう)愛の信徒よ
（スバル）ペテルギウス
Petelgeuse...
My, my, my...
The one you clutch to your chest there
その胸に抱いていらっしゃるのは
ひょっとして―
wouldn't be the half-devil girl, would it?
半魔の娘では
ありませんデスかね？
How diligent you are!
あなたは なんと勤勉なることか！
Before we could even act,
我々が動くより前に―
you took the half-devil's life,
in the Ordeal's name!
半魔の命を 試練にかけて
奪ってくれているとは！
I'm diligent?
（スバル）俺が… 勤勉？
That's right!
ええ そうです！
んんー 勤勉！
You are diligent! Fantastic!
すばらしいデス！
Still...
それにしても―
Unable to overcome even one Ordeal,
試練１つすら乗り越えられず―
much less to confront one of the sins,
あまつさえ 大罪の１つすら
向き合えず―
and after all that waiting...
大望を抱いた挙句に―
She trips over the first pebble
in her path, and it's over...
最初の石ころにつまずいて
終わるとは
Ah, you are
ああ あなた―
truly slothful...
怠惰デスね
You saw the Unseen Hand just now, did you not?
あなた 今―
見えざる手を
見ていませんデスか？
ダメデス ダメなのデス
No...
That's unacceptable.
This isn't right! It's all wrong!
おかしい 間違っている
誤っている！
It's a mistake! A mistake!
過っている！
My Authority...
私の権能を―
The Authority of Sloth...
怠惰の権能を―
My Unseen Hand, which love granted to me...
寵愛によって―
授けられし 私の見えざる手
No other can be allowed to see it!
ほかの誰かが
目にすることなど―
It is for my eyes alone!
許されないのデス！
You held her, as if she were
terribly precious to you.
随分と大事そうに
抱えていたようデスが―
But when the half-devil's body is torn
apart, how beautifully will you cry?
半魔の肉体
破壊したら あなたは―
あなたはどれほどいい声で
鳴いてくれるのデスかねえ
Stop...
や… めろ！
Stop!
やめろー！
（ペテルギウス）アーハハハハ
Please stop!
やめてくれー！
What are you doing?
（パック）何をしている
What are you doing to my daughter,
僕の娘に何をしている
下郎ども
you degenerates?
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme
Disgrace
in the
Extreme